When you are ready, I will surrender
Take me and do as you will
Have what you want, your way's always the best way
I have succumbed to this passive sensation
Peacefully falling away
I am the zombie, your wish will command me
Laugh as I fall to my knees

Bring it back (sing it)
Sing it back (sing it)
Bring it back
Sing it back to meBring it back (sing it)
Sing it back (sing it)
Bring it back
Sing it back to me

Can I control this empty delusion?
Lost in the fire below
And you come running your eyes will be open
And when you come back, I'll be as you want me
Only so eager to please
My little song will keep you beside me
Thinking your name as I sing

Bring it back (sing it)
Sing it back (sing it)
Bring it back
Sing it back to meBring it back (sing it)
Sing it back (sing it)
Bring it back
Sing it back to me

Come to my sweet melody (x2) - yavaşlıyor.No, you can't help it if you have been tempted
By fruit hanging ripe on the tree
And I feel useless
Don't care what the truth is
You will be here come the day
Truth do you hear me?
Don't try to come near me
So tired I sleep through the lie
If you desire to lay here beside me

Bring it back (sing it)
Sing it back (sing it)
Bring it back
Sing it back to meBring it back (sing it)
Sing it back (sing it)
Bring it back
Sing it back to me

Bring it back (sing it)
Sing it back (sing it)
Bring it back
Sing it back to me

Son kez