Ohh Pretty Woman

Oh, oh pretty woman, she's the rising sun
Cheap paint and powder ain't gonna, help you none
She's a pretty woman right down, to the bone
So you might as well, still leave your, skin alone

Pretty woman
What's the matter with you?
Can't make you love me, no
No matter what I do, no

Oh pretty woman, what you, trying to do?
Kept fooling around till I got, stuck on you
You drop that mess, come down, off your throne
Stop using my heart as your, stepping stone

Pretty woman
What's the matter with you?
Can't make you love me, no
No matter what I do

Listen to me, baby
Yeah

Gitar Solo (1tur)

Oh pretty woman, that's all right for you
Just go on doing what you, want to do
But someday when you thing you've, got it made
You'll be in water so deep, you can't wade

Pretty woman
Oh, what's the matter with you?
Can't make you love me, no
No matter what I do, oh, oh yeah

Solo
