You're The One That I WantAm
I got chills
They're multiplying
And I'm losing control
'Cause the power you're supplying
It's electrifying!
4 ölçü

You better shape up
'Cause I need a man
And my heart is set on you
You better shape up
You better understand
To my heart I must be true
Nothing left
Nothing left for me to do

You're the one that I want
Oo-oo-oo, honey
The one that I want
Oo-oo-oo, honey
The one that I want
Oo-oo-oo, the one I need
Oh, yes, indeed

If you're filled
With affection
You're too shy to convey
Meditate in my direction
Feel your way
2 ölçü

I better shape up
'Cause you need a man
I need a man
Who can keep me satisfied
I better shape up
If I'm gonna prove
You better prove
That my faith is justified
Are you sure?
Yes I'm sure down deep inside

[2x]
You're the one that I want
Oo-oo-oo, honey
The one that I want
Oo-oo-oo, honey
The one that I want
Oo-oo-oo, the one I need
Oh, yes, indeed