Saved E

I used to smoke
I used to drink
I used to smoke, drink, and dance the hoochie-coo
I used to smoke and drink
Smoke and drink and dance the hoochie-coo
Whoa yeah
But now I'm standin' on this corner
Prayin' for a-me, and you
Uh-huh

That's why I'm saved (Saved)
I'm saved (Saved)
A-people let me tell you 'bout a kingdom come
You know I'm saved (Saved)
Oh, I'm saved (Saved)
I am gonna preach until you're deaf and dumb
I'm in that soul-savin' army
Beatin' on that big a-bass drum
Whoa, yeah

I used to cuss
I used to fuss
I used to cuss, fuss and boogie all night long
I used to cuss and fuss
Cuss and fuss and boogie, all night long
Whoa, yeah
But now I'm standin' on this corner
I know right-a from wrong
Oh, yeah

That's why I'm saved (Saved)
I'm saved (Saved)
A-people let me tell you 'bout a, kingdom come
You know I'm saved (Saved)
Oh, I'm saved (Saved)
I can-a preach until you're deaf and dumb
I'm in that soul-savin' army
Beatin' on that big a-bass drum
Whoa, yeah


Gitar Solo - 2 tur


I used to lie (Lie)
I used to cheat (Cheat)
I used to lie (Lie), cheat (Cheat) and step on peoples feet
I used to lie and cheat
And lie and cheat and step on peoples feet
Oh yeah
But now I'm steppin' on the glory
Salvation is-a my beat
Whoa, yeah

That's why I'm saved (Saved)
I'm saved (Saved)
A-people let me tell you 'bout a kingdom come
You know I'm saved (Saved)
I'm saved (Saved)
I can-a preach until you're deaf and dumb
I'm in that soul-savin' army
Beatin' on that big a-bass drum
Whoa, yeah

That's why I'm saved (Saved)
I'm saved (Saved)
I'm saved (Saved)
I'm saved (Saved)
I'm saved (Saved)
Oh (Saved)
Ah-oh (Saved)
Ah-oh (Saved)
I'm in that soul-savin' army
Beatin' on that big a-bass drum
Whoa, yeah

I'm saved
Oh yeah
...

I'm in that soul-savin' army
Beatin' on that big a-bass drum

Saved
