Sweet Home Alabama

Big wheels, keep on turning
Carry me home , to see my kin
Singing songs, about the Southland
I miss Ala-ba -my once again
And I think it's a sin, yes

Well I heard mister Young,  sing about her
Well, I heard ole Neil, put her down
Well, I hope Neil Young will remember
A Southern man, don't need him, around anyhow

Sweet home A-la-ba-ma
Where the skies are so blue
Sweet Home A-la-ba-ma
Lord, I'm coming home to you
Gitar Solo

In Birmingham, they love the governor (boo, boo, boo)
Now we all did, what we could do
Now Watergate, does-not boootther me
Does your conscience bother you?
Tell the truth

Sweet home A-la-ba-ma
Where the skies are so blue
Sweet Home A-la-ba-ma
Lord, I'm coming home to you
(Konuşmalı)Here I come Alabama
klavye Solo

Now Muscle Shoals, has got Swampers
And they've been known,  pick a song or two
..Lord they get me off,so much
They pick me up, when I'm feeling blue..Now how about you?


Sweet home A-la-ba-ma
Where the skies are so blue
Sweet Home A-la-ba-ma
Lord, I'm coming home to you
Sweet home Alabama
Oh sweet home baby
Where the skies are so blue
And the guv'nor's true
Sweet Home Alabama
Lordy
Lord, I'm coming home to youKlavye Solo
(Konuşmalı)Yea, yea Montgomery’s, got the answer
