Good Morning Little School Girl : mi

A good, morning little schoolgirl,
can I go home with you?
tell your mama and your daddy,
that I'm a little schoolboy too.

Baby I love you,
I just can't help help myself.

You're so good looking pretty babe,
I don't need nobody else.

Good morning little schoolgirl,
Can I go home with you?
Uh, uh, uh...

I'm gonna leave you baby,
about the break of day
on account of the way you treat me,
I've got to stay a-way.

A good morning little schoolgirl,
can I go home with you?

tell your mama and your daddy,
that I'm a little schoolboy too.

Come on pretty baby,
oh you know I can't help myself.
Uh, uh, uh...

Solo(1 form)

I'm gonna buy me an aeroplane,
to fly all over your town.
And tell everybody baby,
Lord knows you've been putting me down.

I can't stand it babe,
just cannot help myself

Your're so young and pretty,
But you're lovin' somebody else

Come ooon a good morning little schoolgirl,
can I go home with you?
Uh, uh, uh
Oh babe what you do to me,
I can't help myself.

Gitar solo