
Oh lord, wont you buy me, a mercedes benz ?
My friends all drive porsches, I must make amends.
Worked hard, all my lifetime, no help-from my friends,
So lord, wont you buy me, a mercedes benz ?

Oh lord, wont you buy me, a color tv ?
Dialing for dollars, is trying to find me.
I wait for de-livery, each day until three,
So oh lord, wont you buy me, a color tv ?

1 tur gitar

Oh lord, wont you buy me, a night on the town ?
Im counting, on you lord, please dont let me down.
Prove that you love me, and buy the next round,
Oh lord, wont you buy me, a night on the town ?

Gitar solo

Everybody!
Oh lord, wont you buy me a mercedes benz ?
My friends all drive porsches, I must make amends,
Worked hard all my lifetime, no help from my friends,
So oh lord, wont you buy me a mercedes benz ?
Thats it!

Gitar Solo

Everybody!
Oh lord, wont you buy me a mercedes benz ?
My friends all drive porsches, I must make amends,
Worked hard all my lifetime, no help from my friends,
So oh lord, wont you buy me a mercedes benz ?
Thats it!