Well, it's one for the money
Two for the show
Three to get ready
Now go, cat, go

But don't you
Step on my blue suede shoes
Well you can do anything
But stay off of my, blue suede shoes

Well, you can knock me down
Step in my face
Slander my name all, over the place
Well do anything, that you want to do
But uh-uh, honey lay off of them shoes

And don't you, step on my blue suede shoes
Well, you can do anything
But stay off of my blue suede shoes

Gitar Solo (1)

You can burn my house
Steal my car
Drink my liquor
From an old fruit jar
Well do anything that you want to do
But uh-uh, honey lay off of my shoes

And don't you
Step on my blue suede shoes
Well, you can do anything
But stay off of my blue suede shoes

Gitar Solo (1)

_Well, it's one for the money
Two for the show
Three to get ready
Now go, go, go!

But don't you
Step on my blue suede shoes
Well, you can do anything
But stay off of my blue suede shoes

Well, it's
Blue, blue
Blue suede shoes
Blue, blue
Blue suede shoes, yeah!
Blue, blue
Blue, suede shoes, baby
Blue, blue
Blue suede shoes
Well, you can do anything
But stay off of my blue suede shoes