Well, The house is a rockin', don't bother knockin'
Yeah, the house is a rockin', don't bother knockin'
If the house is a rockin', don't bother, come on in

Kick-off your shoes, start losin' the blues
This-old-house ain’t-got, nothin' to lose
Seen it all for years, start spreadin' the news
We got room on the floor, come on baby shake sumpin' loose

Well, the house is a rockin', don't bother knockin'
Yeah, the house is a rockin', don't bother knockin'
Yeah, the house is a rockin', don't bother come on in
Gitar Solo 2

Well, the house is a rockin', don't bother knockin'
Yeah, the house is a rockin', don't bother knockin'
Yeah, the house is a rockin', don't bother come on in

Walkin' up the street, you can hear the sound
Of some bad honky tonkers, really layin' it down
They've seen it all for years, and 'ave got nothin' to lose
So get out on the floor, shii-immy 'til you shake sumpin' loose

Well, the house is a rockin', don't bother knockin'
Yeah, the house is a rockin', don't bother knockin'
Yeah, the house is a rockin', don't bother come on in
I said the house is a rockin', don't bother come on in
