Solo

Ain't no sunshine when she's gone
It's not warm when, she's away
Ain't no sunshine when she's gone
And she's always gone too long, anytime she goes away

[Verse 2]
Wonder this time where she's gone
Wonder if she's gone to stay
Ain't no sunshine when she's gone
And this house just ain't no home, anytime she goes away

[Verse 3]
And I know, I know, I know, I knowI know, I know, I know, I knowI know, I know, I know, I knowI know, I know, I know, I knowI know, I know, I know, I knowI know, I know, I know, I knowI know, I know
Hey I ought to, leave the young, thing alone
But ain't no sunshine when she's gone, anytime she goes away

Solo

[Verse 4]
Ain't no sunshine when she's gone
Only darkness every day
Ain't no sunshine when she's gone
And this house just ain't no home, anytime she goes away

Wonder this time where she's goneWonder if she's gone to stayAin't no sunshine when she's goneAnd this house just ain't no home, anytime she goes away
Anytime she goes away
Anytime she goes away
Anytime she goes away