White shirt now red, my bloody nose
Sleeping, you're on your tippy toes
Creeping around like, no one knows
Think you're so criminal
(Pedal)Bruises, on both my knees for you
Don't say thank you or please
I do what I want when I'm wanting to
My soul? So cynical

x2     So you're a tough guy
         Like it really rough guy
         Just can't get enough guy
         Chest always so puffed guy
         I'm that bad type
         Make your mama sad type
         Make your girlfriend mad tight
         Might seduce your dad type
I'm the bad guy, duh

I'm the bad guy x2

I like it when you take control
Even if you know that you don't
Own me, I'll let you play the role
I'll be your animal
(Pedal)My mommy likes to sing along with me
But she won't sing this song
If she reads all the lyrics
She'll pity the men I know

x2     So you're a tough guy
         Like it really rough guy
         Just can't get enough guy
         Chest always so puffed guy
         I'm that bad type
         Make your mama sad type
         Make your girlfriend mad tight
         Might seduce your dad type
I'm the bad guy, duh

I'm the bad guy, duh x2