Take me now, baby, here as I am
Pull me close, try and understand
Desire is a hunger, is the fire I breathe
Love is a banquet on which we feed

Come on now, try and understand
The way I feel, when I'm in your hands
Take my hand, come undercover
They can't hurt you now
Can't hurt you now, can't hurt you now

Because the night belongs to lovers
Because the night belongs to lust
Because the night belongs to lovers
Because the night belongs to us

Have I doubt, when I'm alone
Love is a ring, the telephone
Love is an angel, disguised as lust
Here in our bed until the morning comes

Come on now try and understand
The way I feel under your command
Take my hand, as the sun descends
They can't touch you now
Can't touch you now, can't touch you now

Because the night belongs to lovers
Because the night belongs to lust
Because the night belongs to lovers
Because the night belongs to us

Gitar solo

With love, we sleep
With doubt, the vicious circle
Turn and burns
Without you, AAY(I) cannot live
Forgive, the year,ning burning
I believe, it's time, too real to feel
So touch me now, touch me now, touch me now

Because the night belongs to lovers
Because the night belongs to lust
Because the night belongs to lovers
Because the night belongs to us

Because tonight there are two lovers
If we believe in the night we trust
Because the night belongs to lovers
Because the night belongs to lust

Solo gitar