Faith sol

See the girl with the diamonds and the shoes? yeah
She walks around like she's got nothin' to lose
Yes she's a go-getter, she's everybody's type
She's a queen of the city but she don't believe the hype
She's got her own elevation, holy motivation
'Til I wrote some letters on big-bold-signs

I got faith, in you baby, I got faith in you now
And you've been such a, such a good friend of me
Know that I love you somehow
I met you, hallelujah, I got faith

See the boy with the Stevie Wonder swag?
Ain't gotta cup all the magic that he has
He's a go-getter, he's everybody's type
I'mma make it my mission, make him feel alright
He's a twelve on a ten point, rockin' out to his joint
Just say the word 'cause I can sing all night

I got faith, in you baby, I got faith, in you now
And you've been such a, such a good friend of me
Know that I love you somehow (love you somehow)
I met you, hallelujah, I got faith

Faith,

Gitar solo (1 tur)

I get it runnin' and my mind goes crazy
I think about you mornin', noon, night and day
I get it runnin' and my mind, goes crazy
I think about you mornin', noon, night
I met you, hallelujah

I got faith in you baby, I got faith in you now
And you've been such a, such a good friend of me
Know that I love you somehow (love you somehow)

I met you, hallelujah, I got faith (faith, faith, baby)
I got faith in you baby, I got faith in you now
And you've been such a, such a good friend of me
Know that I love you somehow (yes I do)
I met you, hallelujah, I met you, hallelujah
I met you, hallelujah, I got faith
