Roadhouse Blues

Yeah

Yeah, keep your eyes on the road, your hand upon the wheel
Keep your eyes on the road, your hand u-pon the wheel
Yeah, we're goin' to the Roadhouse
We're gonna have a ree-aal
Buy Good time
 
Yeah, back at the Roadhouse they got some bungal-oows
Yeah, back at the Roadhouse they got some bunga-loows
And that's for the people
Who like to go down slow

Let it roll, baby, roll
Let it roll, baby, roll
Let it roll, baby, roll
Let it roll, all night long

Do it, Robby, do it

Klavye Solodüşük:
You gotta roll, roll, roll
You gotta thrill my soul, all right
Roll, roll, roll, roll
Thrill my soul
You gotta, beep a gunk a chucha
Honk konk konk
You gotta, each you puna
Each ya, - bop a luba
Each yall bump a kechonk
Ease sum konk
Yeah, ride

Ashen lady, ashen lady
Give up your vows, give up your vows
(Yüksek)Save our citysave our city
Right now

Well, I woke up this morning, I got my-self a beer
Well, I woke up this morning, and I got myself a beer
The future's uncertain, and the end is always near

Let it roll, baby, roll
Let it roll, baby, roll
Let it roll, baby, roll
Let it roll, all night long