Well I'm so above you, it is plain to see
But I came to love you anyway
So you pulled my heart out
And I don't mind bleeding
Any old time you keep me waiting, waiting, waiting

[Chorus]
Oh, oh, oh, oh, I got a love that keeps me waiting
I'm a lonely boy

[Verse 2]
Well your mama kept you but your daddy left you
And I should have done you just the same
But I came to love you
Am I born to bleed?
Any old time you keep me waiting, waiting, waiting

[Chorus]
Oh, oh, oh, oh, I got a love that keeps me waiting
I'm a lonely boy