Mary had a little lamb - Stevie Ray Vaughen: mi

2 form boş dönsün

Mary had a little lamb?
It's fleece was white as - snow, yeah
Everywhere the child went
The lamb, the lamb was sure to go, yeah

He followed her to school one day
And broke the teacher's rule
And what a time did they have
That day at school

Gitar solo - 1 form

Tisket ! - tasket baby
A green and yellow basket
I wrote a letter to my baby
And on my way I passed it

Gitar 1 form

Hit it
