Mustang Sally: do

Mustang Sally, guess you better slow your mustang down
Mustang Sally my baby, guess you better slow your mustang down
You been running all over the town
Oh! I guess I'll have to put your flat, feet on the ground

All you want to do is ride around Sally, ride, Sally, ride
All you want to do is ride around Sally, ride, Sally, ride
All you want to do is ride around Sally, ride, Sally, ride
All you want to do is ride around Sally, ride, Sally, ride
One of these early mornings, I gonna be wiping those ,weeping eyes

I bought you a brand new mustang,  'bout nineteen sixty five
Now you come around, signifying a woman, you don't want to, let me ride
Mustang Sally, guess you better slow your mustang down
You been running all over the town now
Oh! I guess I'll have to put your flat, feet on the ground

All you want to do is ride around Sally, ride, Sally, ride
All you want to do is ride around Sally, ride, Sally, ride
All you want to do is ride around Sally, ride, Sally, ride
All you want to do is ride around Sally, ride, Sally, ride
One of these early mornings, I gonna be wiping those ,weeping eyes

Gitar solo 
Come on boss! Don’t speak tonight?? 

Wiping eyes!!
Those wiping eyes

Those??

All you wanna...,