
Tiz gir:
La la la la
La la la la
La la la la (yeah)
La la la la

I want you to love me,
Like I'm a hot ride (uh yeah)
Keep thinkin' of me (uh)
Doin' what you like
So boy forget about the world
'Cause it's gon' be me and you tonight (yeah)
I wanna make your beg for it
Then I'mma make you swallow, your pride

Want you to make me feel
Like I'm the only girl in the world
Like I'm the only one that, you'll ever love
Like I'm the only one who knows your heart
Only girl in the world
Like I'm the only one that's in command
'Cause I'm the only one who understands
How to make you feel like a man
Yeah
Want you to make me feel
Like I'm the only girl in the world
Like I'm the only one that you'll ever love
Like I'm the only one who knows your heart
Only one

Want you to take it
Like a thief in the night
Hold me like a pillow
Make me feel right
Baby I'll tell you all my secrets
That I'm keepin', you can come inside (yeah)
And when you enter, you ain't leavin'
Be my prisoner for the night, oh

Want you to make me feel
Like I'm the only girl in the world
Like I'm the only one that you'll ever love
Like I'm the only one who knows your heart
Only girl in the world
Like I'm the only one that's in command
'Cause I'm the only one who understands
Like I'm the only one who knows your heart
Only one

Take me for a ride, ride
Oh baby, take me high, high
Let me make you rise, rise
Oh make it last all night, night

Take me for a ride, ride
Oh baby, take me high, high
Let me make you rise, rise
Make it last all night

Want you to make me feel
Like I'm the only girl in the world
Like I'm the only one that you'll ever love
Like I'm the only one who knows your heart
Only girl in the world
Like I'm the only one that's in command
'Cause I'm the only one who understands
How to make you feel like a man
Only girl in the world
Girl in the world
Only girl in the world
Girl in the world