Something’s gotta hold on me:  do

Oh sometimes I get a good feeling yeah
I get a feeling that I never, never had before
And I got to tell you right now
I believe, I really do believe that

Something's got a hold on me (oh, it must be love)
Something's got a hold on me right now child (yeah, it must be love)

Let me tell you now
I got a feeling, I feel so strange
Everything about me seems to have changed
Step by step, I got a brand new walk
I even sound sweeter when I talk

I said, oh, oh, oh, oh
I said baby, oh, it must be love (you know it must be love)

Let me tell you now
Something’s got a hold on me, yeah (oh, it must be love)
Oh oh something’s got a hold on me right now, child (Oh, it must be love)

Let me tell you now
I never felt like this before
Something’s got a hold on me that won’t let go
I believe I’d die if I only could
I sure feel strange, but it sure feels good

I said, oh, oh, oh, oh
I said baby, oh, it must be love (you know it must be love)

Let me tell you know
My heart feels heavy, my feet feel light
I shake all over, but I feel alright
I never felt like this before
Something’s got a hold on me that won’t let go
I never thought it could happen to me
Got me heavy without the misery
I never thought it could be this way
Love’s sure gonna put a hurting on me

I said, oh, oh, oh, oh
I said baby, oh, it must be love (you know it must be love) 
Yeah, he walks like love (you know he walks like love)
He talks like love (you know he talks like love)
Makes me feel alright (makes me feel alright)
In the middle of the night (in the middle of the night)

Na na la la (na na la la)
Na na la la (na na la la)
Na na la laNa na lalaPara bailar la bamba
Para bailar la bamba se necesita una poca de gracia
Una poca de gracia pa' mi pa' ti y arriba y arriba
Ah y arriba y arriba por ti seré, por ti seré, por ti seré

Yo no soy marinero
Yo no soy marinero, soy capitán,
Soy capitán, soy capitán

Bamba bamba

Para bailar la bamba
Para bailar la bamba se necesita una poca de gracia
Una poca de gracia pa' mi pa' ti ah y arriba y arriba

Para bailar la bamba
Para bailar la bamba se necesita una poca de gracia
Una poca de gracia pa' mi pa' ti ah y arriba y arriba
Ah y arriba y arriba por ti seré, por ti seré, por ti seré

Bamba bamba

