When the night has come
And the land is dark
And the moon, is the only light, we'll see
No, I won't be afraid
Oh, I won't be afraid
Just as long, as you stand
Stand by me

So darlin', darlin'
Stand by me, oh, stand by me
Oh, stand, stand by me
Stand by me

If the sky, that we look upon
Should tumble and fall
Or the mountain, should crumble, to the sea
I won't cry, I won't cry
No I won’t, shed a tear
Just as long, as you stand
Stand by me

And darlin', darlin'
Stand by me, oh, stand by me
Oh, stand now, stand by me
Stand by me

Solo 2 tur

If the sky that we look upon
Should tumble and fall
Or the mountain, should crumble, to the sea
I won't cry, I won't cry
No, I won’t, shed a tear
Just as long, as you stand
Stand by me

2xDarlin', darlin'
Stand by me, oh, stand by me
Oh, stand now, stand by me
Stand by me
Darlin', darlin'
Stand by me, oh, stand by me
Oh, stand now, stand by me
Stand by me