Where's all my soul sistas?
Lemme hear ya'll flow, sistasHey sista, go sista, soul sista, flow sista
Hey sista, go sista, soul,

He met Marmalade down in old Moulin Rouge
Struttin’ her stuff on the street
She said, "Hello, hey Jo, you wanna give it a go?" Oh! uh huh

Giuchie, Giuchie, ya ya dada (Hey hey hey)
Giuchie, Giuchie, ya ya here (Here)
Mocha Chocalata ya ya (Oh yea)
Creole lady Marmalade

Voulez vous coucher avec moi ce soir
Voulez vous coucher avec moi

He sat in her boudoir while she, freshened up
Boy drank all that Magnolia wine
On her black satin sheets, is where he started to freak, yeah

Giuchie, Giuchie, ya ya dada (Da-da-da)
Giuchie, Giuchie, ya ya here (Here ooh yeah yeah)
Mocha Choca lata ya ya (Yeah)
Creole lady Marmalade

Voulez vous coucher avec moi ce soir (Ce soir, what what what)
Voulez vous coucher avec moi

Yea yea uh
We come, through with the money and the, garter belts
Let him know we bout that cake, straight out the gate uh
We independent women, some mistake us for whores
Why spend mine, when I can spend yours?
Disagree? Well that's you and, I’m sorry
Imma keep playing these cats out, like Atari
high heel shoes, getting love from the dudes
Four bad ass chicks, from the Moulin Rouge

We drink wine with diamonds in the glass
By the case, the meaning of expensive taste
Giuche giuch ya ya
Mocha Chocalate-a what?
Creole Lady Marmalade

Marmalade,
Lady Marmalade,
Marmalade
Hey, hey, hey

Touch of her skin feeling silky smooth
Color of cafe au lait alright
Made the savage beast inside roar until he cried,
More, more, more

Now he's back home doin' 9 to 5
Sleepin' the grey flannel life
But when he turns off to sleep memories creep,
More, more, more

Giuchie, Giuchie, ya ya dada (Da-da-da)
Giuchie, Giuchie, ya ya here (Here ooh yeah yeah)
Mocha Choca lata ya ya (Yeah)
Creole lady Marmalade