
2 tur bos
+
2 tur gitarli

I didn't mean to end his life, I know it wasn't right
I can't even sleep at night, can't get it off my mind
I need to get out of sight, fore I end up behind bars

What started out as a simple altercation
Turned in-to a real sticky situation
Me just thinking on the time, that I'm facing
Makes me wanna cry

'Cause I didn't mean to hurt him
Coulda been somebody's son
And I took his heart when
I pulled out that gun

Rum bum bum bum, rum bum bum bum, rum bum bum bum
Man Down!
Rum bum bum bum, rum bum bum, bum rum bum bum bum
Man Down!

Oh mama, mama, mama
I just shot a man down
In central station
In front of a big ol' crowd
Oh, why? oh, why?
Oh mama mama mama
I just shot a man down

Little 22, I call her Peggy Sue
When she fits right down in my shoes
Whatchu expect me to do? if you're playing me, for a fool
I will lose my cool, and reach for my fire arm

I didn't mean to lay him down
But its too late to turn back nooooooow
Don't know what I was thinking
Now he's no longer living
So I'm bout to leave town

'Cause I didn't mean to hurt him
Coulda been somebody's son
And I took his heart when
I pulled out that gun

Rum bum bum bum, rum bum bum bum, rum bum bum bum
Man Down!
Rum bum bum bum, rum bum bum, bum rum bum bum bum
Man Down!

Oh mama, mama, mama
I just shot a man down
In central station
In front of a big ol' crowd
Oh, why? Oh, why?
Oh mama, mama, mama, I just shot a man down 

Said, "I'd never thought I'd do it
Never thought I'd do it, never thought I'd do it!
Oh gosh, What ever happened to me
Ever happened to me, ever happened to me?
Why did I pull the trigger, pull the trigger, pull the trigger? Boom
And end a nigga, end a nigga life so soon?
When mi pull the trigger, pull the trigger, pull it pon' you
Somebody tell me what I'm gonna, what I'm gonna do? Ehh

Rum bum bum bum, rum bum bum bum, rum bum bum bum
Man Down!
Rum bum bum bum, rum bum bum, bum rum bum bum bum
Man Down!  

Oh mama, mama, mama
I just shot a man down
In central station
In front of a big ol crowd
Oh, why? Oh, why?
Oh mama, mama, mama
I just shot a man down